Lish mss., 1951-2017 LMC 2404
Lilly Library
- II. Writings
  - Additional Writings
    - Allen, Jeff. Stories (Box 103)
      - A Brooklyn Clean and Well-Lighted: A Review of Nicholas Montemarano's A Fine Place (Box 103)
      - Used to Do (Box 103)
      - Shadowboxing (Box 103)
      - Toilet Training (Box 103)
      - Mississippi Story (Box 103)
      - Dog Tags (Box 103)
    - Arnoldi, Katherine (Box 103)
      - All Things Are Labor (Box 103)
    - Baird, Ansie. Poems, (2 folders) (Box 103)
      - And So It Was (Box 103)
      - News from the Ramparts (Box 103)
      - Breathing Lessons (Box 103)
      - Forecast (Box 103)
      - The Earth in Its Orbit (Box 103)
      - Times Two (Box 103)
      - A Partial Story (Box 103)
      - Plain Song (Box 103)
      - The Royal Connection (Box 103)
      - The Line (Box 103)
      - The Statue (Box 103)
      - The Earth in its Orbit (Box 103)
    - Baricco, Alessandro, (3 folders) (Box 103)
      - Penguin City (Box 103)
    - Bass, Rick (Box 103)
      - Not Home (Box 103)
    - Blanchard, Richard (Box 103)
      - Doing the High Traverse (Box 103)
    - Borges, Jorge Luis (Box 103)
      - An Overwhelming Film (on Citizen Kane) (Box 103)
    - Brodkey, Harold (Box 103)
      - Preface (Box 103)
    - Buckner, Garth, (5 folders) (Box 103)
    - Bangalay (Box 103)
      - The Lion in our Garden (Box 103)
      - The Origins of Solitude (Box 103)
      - The Human Tide (Box 103)
    - Carrollhach, Haley. Stories, (8 folders) (Box 103)
      - Beautiful Daughters (Box 103)
      - Magnificent Odessa (Box 103)
      - Her Hogs (Box 103)
      - Suddenly Yellow (Box 103)
      - The Party (Box 103)
      - Teenagers in Loveland (Box 103)
      - A Betrayal (Box 103)
      - Deaf Strength (Box 103)
      - Killing Chickens (Box 103)
      - They Feared Mountain Lion (Box 103)
      - Precious and Precious's Mother (Box 103)
      - Teenagers in Loveland (Box 103)
      - Killing Chickens (Box 103)
      - The Joseph Story (Box 103)
      - Deaf Strength (Box 103)
      - Suddenly Yellow (Box 103)
      - My Grandfather and the Telephone (Box 103)
      - Magnificent Odessa (Box 103)
      - The First Half of Summer (Box 103)
      - A Harvest of Cabbage (Box 103)
      - The Impossible Bottom (Box 103)
      - A Harvest of Cabbage (Box 103)
      - The End of the Bible (Box 103)
      - The Neighborhood (Box 103)
      - My Mother Said (Box 103)
      - Many Such Afternoons (Box 103)
      - The Inheritance (Box 103)
      - The Get-Together (Box 103)
      - Décor (Box 103)
      - An Inheritance (Box 103)
      - The End of the Bible (Box 103)
      - Untitled (Box 103)
      - Killing Chickens (Box 103)
      - Corn (Box 103)
      - The Word STOP Mirrored in Water (Box 103)
      - Endings Go Down Drains (Box 103)
    - Carver, George (Box 104)
      - Lish, Gordon: Notes and Reflections of a Former Student (Box 104)
    - Cooperrider, Carrie. Stories (Box 104)
      - The Book Bug (Box 104)
      - Out West (Box 104)
    - Corman, Catherine (Box 104)
      - Appraiser, Reappraised or Three Books (Box 104)
      - Collecting Venus: Citizen Kane's Solitude (Box 104)
    - Cuiff, Jules (Box 104)
      - Cirque du Calder (Box 104)
    - deCourcy, Lynne H. Poems. (Box 104)
      - Sister, Did You Ever Pray? (Box 104)
      - Watching My Daughter Skate: In Training (Box 104)
      - Searching (Box 104)
    - DeLillo, Don, (4 folders) (Box 104)
      - That Day in Rome (Box 104)
      - Beader-Meinhof (Box 104)
      - S/11: Making War on the Future (Box 104)
      - Woman in the Distance (Box 104)
    - Doran, Cat (Box 104)
      - Some Girls (Box 104)
    - Durando, Neal (Box 104)
      - F105 over Red River (Box 104)
    - Engels, John. Poems (Box 104)
      - The Warning (Box 104)
      - Devil's Hole (Box 104)
    - Eno, Will. Plays, (2 folders) (Box 104)
      - Ladies and Gentleman (Box 104)
      - King Anyone (Box 104)
      - Middletown (Box 104)
    - Eno, Will. Stories, (2 folders) (Box 104)
      - Wild (Box 104)
      - Fast Living (Box 104)
      - Interview with Berkeley Rep Magazine (Box 104)
    - Evenson, Brian, (3 folders) (Box 104)
      - Difficult Communions (Box 104)
      - The Open Curtain (Box 104)
    - Feldman, Irving. Poems (Box 104)
      - Poet at Thirteen (Box 104)
      - Yet Even These (Box 104)
    - Foulkrod, Catherine (Box 104)
      - For the Day (Box 104)
    - Froderberg, Gretchen (Box 104)
      - Various Live Death Acts (Box 104)
    - Froderberg, Susan. Stories (Box 104)
      - A Home to Go Home To (Box 104)
      - Old Border Road (Box 104)
    - Froterberg, Gretchen (Box 104)
      - Aiea Heights (Box 104)
      - Among the Living (Box 104)
      - 86th-96th-76th (Box 104)
      - Gretchen Froterberg (Box 104)
      - The Story of Grout (Box 104)
    - Gaddis, Anicee (Box 104)
      - Untitled (Box 104)
    - Hannah, Barry (Box 104)
      - Repulsed (Box 104)
      - Untitled (Box 104)
    - Gilbert, Jack (Box 104)
      - Refusing Heaven (Box 104)
    - Hanshe, Rainer J. (Box 104)
      - The Acolytes (Box 104)
    - Hempel, Amy. Stories (Box 104)
      - The Uninvited (Box 104)
      - Melody (Box 104)
      - Mouths, Open (Box 104)
      - Untitled (Box 104)
      - Sing To It (Box 104)
      - Greed (Box 104)
    - Holland, Noy. Stories, (2 folders) (Box 104)
      - Time for the Flat-Headed Man (Box 104)
      - Visitations (Box 104)
      - What Begins with Bird (Box 104)
      - Fairway (Box 104)
      - Swim for the Little One First (Box 104)
    - Holodnak, Lili (Box 104)
      - Untitled (Box 104)
    - Jackson, Mitchell S. (Box 104)
      - In John We Trust (Box 104)
      - The Residue Years (Box 104)
      - Untitled (Box 104)
    - Jiles, Paulette (Box 104)
      - Untitled (Box 104)
    - Kamine, Mark (Box 104)
      - The Blow (Box 104)
    - Kimball, Michael. Poems (Box 104)
      - Remains of the Day (Box 104)
      - If You Leave the Door Open (Box 104)
      - The Jortian Age (Box 104)
    - Knauff, Marco (Box 104)
      - Six Dramantics (Box 104)
    - Lear, Patricia. Stories, (4 folders) (Box 105)
      - No One Will Ever Marry You, You Know (Box 105)
      - Nirvana (Box 105)
      - The Bridge Playing Ladies (Box 105)
      - After Memphis (Box 105)
      - Summer Party (Box 105)
      - Nirvana (Box 105)
      - Nirvana (Box 105)
      - Interview: Amy Hempel (Box 105)
    - Lemann, Nancy (Box 105)
      - The Undeparted (Box 105)
    - Lentricchia, Frank (Box 105)
      - Disappearance (Box 105)
      - The Italian Actress (Box 105)
      - Aristotle and/or DeLillo (Box 105)
    - Levine, Jeffrey (Box 105)
      - Distinguished Guests (Box 105)
    - Lingis, Alphoso (Box 105)
      - Trust (Box 105)
    - Lock, Norman, (6 folders) (Box 105)
      - Favorite Sports of the Martyrs (Box 105)
      - The Captain is Sleeping (Box 105)
      - A Swan Boat on the Nile (Box 105)
      - Love in the Steam Age (Box 105)
      - The Sleep Institute (Box 105)
      - Marco and Marian Take a Vacation (Box 105)
      - Marco and Marion Sleep (Box 105)
      - Tango in Amsterdam (Box 105)
      - The Light on the Razorwire is almost Beautiful (Box 105)
      - Love in the Steam Age (Box 105)
      - The Monster in Winter (Box 105)
      - To Each According to His Sentence (Box 105)
      - Scenes in the Life of Napoleon Bonaparte (Box 105)
      - In the Time of the Comet (Box 105)
      - My Father's Affair with Esther Williams (Box 105)
      - The Invisible Dutchman and His Dog (Box 105)
      - The Gaiety of Henry James (Box 105)
      - From Piece for Small Orchestra (Box 105)
      - The Havoc of the Stars/The Universe of the Body (Box 105)
      - Ideas of Space (Box 105)
      - The King of Sweden (Box 105)
    - Loomis, Edward (Box 105)
      - Homeward (Box 105)
    - Long, Daniel (Box 105)
      - Homework (Box 105)
      - Untitled (Box 105)
    - Lutz, Gary (Box 105)
      - Impossible Object (Box 105)
      - Fatal Agreement (Box 105)
      - Stories in the Worst Way (Box 105)
      - An Interview with Gary Lutz (Box 105)
    - Maliszewski, Paul (Box 105)
      - Actual Value (Box 105)
      - Facsimile (Box 105)
      - Harvey Strub (Box 105)
    - Manning, Kate (Box 105)
      - Found (Box 105)
    - Margalit, Israela (Box 105)
      - Getting Noticed (or not) book proposal (Box 105)
    - Marten, Eugene (Box 106)
      - In the Blind (Box 106)
    - Marten, Eugene (Box 106)
      - In the Blind (Box 106)
      - Rat of the World (Box 106)
    - Meissner, Jan, (2 folders) (Box 106)
      - Zoomtown (Box 106)
    - Michel, Sam (Box 106)
    - Michel, Sam, (3 folders) (Box 106)
      - Lincoln Dahl Turns Fire (Box 106)
      - Big Dogs and Flyboys (Box 106)
    - Mikesch, Elizabeth (Box 106)
      - Saturnine (Box 106)
    - Miller, S.G. (Box 106)
      - Old Hildegarde Has Died (Box 106)
      - Paradise (Box 106)
    - Millhauser, Steven (Box 106)
      - Edwin Mullhouse (Box 106)
    - Mirsky, Mark Jay (Box 106)
      - A Dish of Radishes (Box 106)
    - Montgomery, Mark (Box 106)
      - A Locomotive in Winter (Box 106)
    - Moore, Honor (Box 106)
      - The Pink Dress (Box 106)
    - Mulcahy, Greg, (4 folders) (Box 107)
      - Canada (Box 107)
      - Carbine (Box 107)
      - Fishing Trips (Box 107)
      - Sustenance (Box 107)
    - Murphy, Yannick (Box 107)
      - Here Come the Hot Dog Men (Box 107)
    - Newman, Leigh. Stories, (2 folders) (Box 107)
      - I Know How You Are (Box 107)
      - My Father's Best Friend's Daughter (Box 107)
      - One Bedroom (Box 107)
      - Dad's Piano (Box 107)
      - The Blasphemer of Spices (Box 107)
      - Eat (Box 107)
      - A Little More History (Box 107)
      - Child? Dog? Stay? Run? (Box 107)
      - That Water (Box 107)
      - Our Night Out (Box 107)
      - His Call (Box 107)
      - You Know the Story (Box 107)
      - Just as Soon as She Wakes Up (Box 107)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol (Box 107)
      - How My Father Was Murdered (Box 107)
    - O'Connell, Patricia, (2 folders) (Box 107)
      - Night Windows (Box 107)
    - Ozick, Cynthia, (2 folders) (Box 107)
      - (to Q) Reply to an Invitation (All Expenses Paid) to Germany (Box 107)
      - The Modern Hep! Hep! Hep! (Box 107)
    - Pendleton, Jan. Stories (Box 107)
      - Movers (Box 107)
      - Iguanas (Box 107)
      - Dummies (Box 107)
      - Sarah (Box 107)
    - Pinson, David. Stories (Box 107)
      - This is When (Box 107)
      - Departures (Box 107)
      - Storage (Box 107)
      - The Wake (Box 107)
      - Bandage (Box 107)
    - Raffel, Dawn, (3 folders) (Box 107)
      - Further Adventures in the Restless Universe (Box 107)
      - The Lesson (Box 107)
      - Carrying the Body (Box 107)
    - Rauch, Earl (Box 107)
      - The Wonderful World of DeSoto (Box 107)
    - Rayfiel, Tom (Box 107)
      - Ideograms (Box 107)
    - Redel, Victoria (Box 107)
      - I Could See for a While Who Was Who (Box 107)
    - Rehill, Evan, (2 folders) (Box 107)
      - The Runner (Box 107)
      - The Spade (Box 107)
    - Renner, Cooper. Poems, (2 folders) (Box 107)
      - Bedtime Story (Box 107)
      - Ceasarean (Box 107)
      - [Untitled] (Box 107)
    - Richard, Mark, (3 folders) (Box 108)
      - The Ice at the Bottom of the World (Box 108)
    - Rodriguez, Jesus Ramon. Stories, (2 folders) (Box 108)
      - La Cosa Grande (Box 108)
      - Genio (Box 108)
      - Meat Cutter (Box 108)
      - Wife (Box 108)
    - Rybicki, John. Interview, Poems, Stories, (4 folders) (Box 108)
      - Delicious Vertigo: A Conversation with John Rybicki (Box 108)
      - The Boy (Box 108)
      - I Pass This Beautiful Crow (Box 108)
      - Into the Standing Corn (Box 108)
      - Yellow Jackets (Box 108)
      - Brother (Box 108)
      - I Straddle the Earth (Box 108)
      - Firstling (Box 108)
      - These Nail Holes in my Palm (Box 108)
      - I Reach Through the Cobwebs, Ice and Weariness (Box 108)
      - My Animal (Box 108)
      - Why Everything is a Poem (Box 108)
      - Day Seven in the Belly of the Whale - Bone Marrow Unit, October 23, 1994 (Box 108)
      - Lifting My Bride (Box 108)
      - Daily this Leaf Blown (Box 108)
      - Thought at the Parting of These Waters (Box 108)
      - There's No Place on this Earth Quiet Enough (Box 108)
      - It's Morning and I'm Trying on the Walls (Box 108)
      - Quarter (Box 108)
      - Love is the Heel That Knocks Hard Against the Floor (Box 108)
      - Yellow-Haired Girl with Spider (Box 108)
    - Ryder, Pamela (Box 108)
      - A Tendency to be Gone (Box 108)
    - Ryder, Pamela, (5 folders) (Box 108)
      - Captiva (Box 108)
      - The Correction of Drift (Box 108)
      - Graveweed (Box 108)
      - Recognizable Constellations and Familiar Objects of the Night Sky in Early (Box 108)
    - Spring (Box 108)
      - Untitled (Box 108)
    - Spargo, R. Clifton. Stories (Box 108)
      - All Her Sons are Fallen (Box 108)
      - The Empty Center (Box 108)
      - The Breach (Box 108)
    - St. Germain, Richard (Box 108)
      - Chrysanthemums (Box 108)
      - Loveseat (Box 108)
    - Steinberg, Susan. Stories (Box 108)
      - Adult (Box 108)
      - Lifelike (Box 108)
    - Sudnow, David (Box 108)
      - I Could Write a Book (Box 108)
    - Taylor, Justin (Box 108)
      - In My Heart I am Already Gone (Box 108)
    - Trelawny, Victor. Stories (Box 108)
      - In the Land of Opportunity (Box 108)
      - My First Three Visits with Her (Box 108)
      - About Australia (Box 108)
      - In the Basement (Box 108)
    - Udelson, Jonathan. Stories (Box 108)
      - All the Gathered, Here Again (Box 108)
    - Updike, John (Box 108)
      - The Tarbox Police (Box 108)
    - Volk, Patricia (Box 108)
      - Stuffed: Adventures of a Restaurant Family (Box 108)
    - Wickersham, Joan (Box 108)
      - The News from Spain (Box 108)
    - Williams, Tennessee (Box 108)
      - Unidentified (Box 108)
    - General, 1990 (Box 116)
    - General, 1992 (Box 116)
    - General, 1993 (Box 116)
    - General, 1994 (Box 116)
    - General, 1995 (Box 116)
    - General, 1996 (Box 116)
    - General, 1997 (Box 116)
    - General, 1998 (Box 116)
    - General, 1999 (Box 116)
    - General, 2000 (Box 116)
    - General, 2004 (Box 116)
    - General, 2006 (Box 116)
    - General, 2008 (Box 116)
    - General, 2009 (Box 116)
    - General, 2010 (Box 116)
    - General, 2012 (Box 116)
    - General, undated (Box 116)
    - Anonymous Authors (Box 117)
      - Act One (Box 117)
      - Five of a Kind (Box 117)
      - Losing My Accent (Box 117)
      - Pleasant Avenue (Box 117)
      - Miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 117)
      - Untitled (Box 117)
    - Miscellaneous Writings, (8 folders) (Box 117)
    - All Our Secrets Are the Same: New Fiction From Esquire mock-ups (Box 118)
    - Unidentified auhor, story notes (Box 128)
- III. Newspaper Clippings
  Contains clippings from newspapers, magazines and periodicals.
  - Carver, 1976, Jan. - Jun. (Box 99)
  - Lish, 1976, Nov. - 1977, Nov.; (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Salinger material, 1977, Jan. - Apr.; (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Forest fires, 1933-1977; (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - 1963, Jan. - 1975, Oct. (Box 99)
  - 1971-1983 (Box 99)
  - ca. 1972-1976 (Box 99)
  - 1974-1976 (Box 99)
  - 1975 (Box 99)
  - 1976 (Box 99)
  - 1977, Jan. - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - 1977, Jan. - Dec. (Box 99)
  - 1978, Apr. - Jul. (Box 99)
  - 1970s (Box 99)
  - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Barry Hannah, 1978, Mar. - Jun. (Box 100)
  - Victor Herman, 1979, Mar.9 (Box 100)
  - Janet Kauffman, 1989, Sept. (Box 100)
  - The Secret Life of Our Times, 1973-1974 (Box 100)
  - 1968-1972 (Box 100)
  - 1970-1979 (Box 100)
  - 1972-1976, Apr. (Box 100)
  - 1973-1975 (Box 100)
  - 1976, May - Jul. (Box 100)
  - 1977-1979 (Box 100)
  - 1977-1984 (Box 100)
  - 1979, Jun. - Fall (Box 100)
  - Printed material and miscellaneous reviews, 1974-1979 (Box 100)
  - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Undated (Box 100)
  - 1970s, (4 folders) (Box 109)
  - and, 1970s; 1980s (Box 109)
  - 1980s (Box 109)
  - 1990s, (2 folders) (Box 109)
  - 1970s (Box 110)
  - 1970s-2000s (Box 110)
  - 1980s (Box 110)
  - 1982, Feb. - May (Box 110)
  - 1985 (Box 110)
  - 1986 (Box 110)
- IV. Photographs
  - Miscellaneous photographs, (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - Etched copper photo printing plate (Box 110)
  - Gordon Lish (Box 115)
  - Samuel Becket (Box 115)
  - Saul Bellow (Box 115)
  - Raymond Carver (Box 115)
  - Neal Cassady (Box 115)
  - James Dickey (Box 115)
  - Ken Kesey (Box 115)
  - Tom Wolfe (Box 115)
  - Esquire (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 115)
  - Slides (Box 115)
  - Unidentified, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Unidentified male (Box 127)
- V. Artwork
  - Miscellaneous drawings and sketches (Box 110)
  - Sketchpads, (3 folders) (Box 113)
  - Drawings Rose Graubart Ignatow, 1952-1965 (Box 113)
  - Marion Perkins Fan Club Scrapbook (Box 113)
  - Artwork and sketches (Box 129)
  - B. Lish (Box 131)
  - All the Pretty Isms for Gordon from Shelton (Box 132)
- VI. Legal
  - Lish v. Harper's, court transcript, 9 Oct. 1992 (Box 110)
  - Lish v. Harper's, court filing, 2 Nov. 1992 (Box 110)
  - Lish v. Harper's, court filing, 5 Nov. 1992 (Box 110)
  - Lish v. Harper's, court filing, 6 Nov. 1992 (Box 110)
  - Lish v. Harper's, court filing, 16 Nov. 1992 (Box 110)
  - Lish v. Harper's, court filing, 24 Nov. 1992 (Box 110)
  - Bernard Geis Assoc. Inc., Publishing Agreement (Box 110)
  - Book Agreement: Raymond Carver and McGraw-Hill Put Yourself in My Shoes (Box 110)
- VII. Realia
  - Party gifts from Norman Lock (Box 118)
  - Gordon Lish's belt (Box 124)
- VIII. Audio-visual
  - Gordon Lish on The Dick Cavett Show videotape (Box 121)
  - I.F. Reading CD-ROM (2) (Box 121)
  - Bookworm Interview CD-ROM (Box 121)
  - Reefer Songs CD-ROM (Box 121)
  - The Best of Everything master-tape (Box 121)
  - The Piano Player master-tape (Box 121)
  - Sunday Dinner in Brooklyn master-tape (Box 121)
  - Victor Herman autobiography, audiocassettes (Box 121)
  - Miscellaneous authors, audiocassettes (Box 121)
  - New Sounds in Fiction master-tapes (11) (Box 122)
  - Student audiotapes, Gordon Lish's classes, 1985-1987 (Box 123)
- IX. Miscellaneous
  - Pamphlets (Box 110)
  - PR materials, (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - Gordon Lish Writing Workshop materials (Box 110)
  - Handwritten journal, unidentified author (Box 110)
  - Letter of recommendation for Evan Sark (Box 110)
  - Maggot Brain No. 2 (Box 110)
  - Midnight Express production notes (Box 110)
  - Publicity materials: A Public Reading, Lecture, and Discussion by Gordon Lish (Box 110)
  - Song Titles (Box 110)
  - Doubleday Catalog (Box 110)
  - Magazines (Box 110)
  - Ephemera (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, (3 folders) (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1987 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1990-1992 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1991-1992; (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1993; (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1994 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1995; (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1996 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1997-1998 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1999 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous papers, undated, (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - Questionnaire responses, 1969 (Box 113)
  - Questionnaire results, responses, 1970 (Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1970s; (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1980s (Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1990s (Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 113)
  - Esquire Merit Award and Pennant, 1974 (Box 114)
  - Maps (Box 114)
  - Pamphlets, 1984 (Box 114)
  - Printed materials, 1970-1976; (2 folders) (Box 114)
  - Printed materials and pamphlets, 1970-1972 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1970s; (4 folders) (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1973 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1974 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1974-1979 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1976 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1977 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1986 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1988 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1980s (Box 114)
  - List: Collection of Published Writings of Gordon Lish, 1956-1987 (Box 115)
  - Project Fire, 1978 (Box 115)
  - Magazines (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1973 (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1976-1977 (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1970s; (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1982 (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1989-1990 (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1980s; (3 folders) (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papersand, 1980s; 1990s (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1990s (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 2000-2010 (Box 115)
  - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 115)
  - Broadsides (Box 127)
    - Lecture by Gordon Lish (Box 127)
    - Contemporary Writing World: A Conversation with Gordon Lish, Lee Eisenberg, John Herrmann (Box 127)
  - Certificate The Art Directors Club 66th Annual Exhibition 1987 Merit Award: Gordon Lish, Editor, 'The Quarterly, Spring 1987' (Box 127)
  - Araby envelope (Box 130)
- X. Additions
  - Additional Correspondence (Box 133)
    - Allman, John and Eileen, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Andreou, George, 2013-2014 (Box 133)
    - Baird, Ansie, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Ballybung, Jim and Liz, 2013, undated (Box 133)
    - Bass, Rick, 2013-2014 (Box 133)
    - Belden, Kathryn, 2012-2014 (Box 133)
    - Blanchard, Richard, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Boland, Eavan, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Buckley, Christopher, 2014 (Box 133)
    - Buckner, Garth, 2012-2013 (Box 133)
    - Cooperrider, Carrie [Fenimore], 2012-2014, undated (Box 133)
    - Corman, Catherina Ann, 2010-2013 (Box 133)
    - Davies, Jeremy M., 2012 (Box 133)
    - Davis, Melinda, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Diebsonovich, Puehle, undated (Box 133)
    - Dieckmann, Katherine, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Donoghue, Denis, 2014 (Box 133)
    - Durat, Marion, 2011 (Box 133)
    - Einhorn, Sharone, 2014 (Box 133)
    - Elliott, Anne, 2012-2013, undated (Box 133)
    - Eno, Will, 2013, undated (Box 133)
    - Feldman, Irving, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Geeslin, Campbell, 2008-2014, undated (Box 133)
    - Gekiere, Nemi, 2012-2014 (Box 133)
    - Glover, Douglas, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Goebel, Luke, 2012, undated (Box 133)
    - Groenland, Tim, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Haag, Peter, 2014 (Box 133)
    - Hach, Haley, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Hade, George, undated (Box 133)
    - Hale, Buddy, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Hamiliton, Mary, 2012-2013, undated (Box 133)
    - Hamilton, Megan, 2011-2012 (Box 133)
    - Hempel, Amy, 2010-2013, undated (Box 133)
    - Hess, Wayne (Larry), 2012 (Box 133)
    - Hintze, Erich, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Hodges, John, 2013-2014 (Box 133)
    - Hogan, Wayne, 2011-2014; (2 folders) (Box 133)
    - Holoboff, Elaine, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Ives, Stephen G., 2013 (Box 133)
    - Jilesjohnson, Paulette, 2012-2014, undated (Box 133)
    - Jackson, Mitchell, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Krupp, Jane, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Lafontaine, Elan, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Landis, Joanne, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Lear, Trish, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Lee, J, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Lemann, Nancy, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Lingis, Al, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Lish, Gordon, 2004-2012, undated (Box 133)
    - Livingstone, Carolyn, 2012-2013 (Box 133)
    - Long, Daniel, 2009 (Box 133)
    - Lutz, Gary, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Mahon, Eugene J., 2013-2014 (Box 133)
    - Maliszewski, Paul, 2012-2014 (Box 133)
    - Marx, Leon, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Mc Auliffe, Jody, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Mc Lendon, David, 2012-2014 (Box 133)
    - Michaka, Stéphane, 2012-2013 (Box 133)
    - Mizrahi, Shevaun, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Mulcahy, Gregory, 2012-2014 (Box 133)
    - O'Connell, Pat, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Odell, Joshua S., 2012 (Box 133)
    - O'Donoghue, Mary, 2012-2013 (Box 133)
    - OR Books, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Ozick, Cynthia, 2008-2014 (Box 133)
    - Parker, Ryan, 2014 (Box 133)
    - Parker, Scott F., 2012 (Box 133)
    - Parsons, Kimberly K., 2009-2010 (Box 133)